[{"answer": "Chancellor", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I got the message you called too", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Trip? ", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Left you...?  Who? my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "my friend left me this morning", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "She's left the room before. She always came back", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "No. Maybe. I don't know. I don't know what I'm going to do", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "And? Are you going to tell him", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " Neither do 1", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Fascinating. Listen, why don't you come out with us after the lecture. There's a place on the Hill I always get Trip to take me", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Oh, don't be silly. No one your age just wants to go home. Besides, faculty will be present. Just think of it as a field trip", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " Go ahead", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Really", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "You", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Does she want to hear it was one of her professors", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Disturbed. And when your friend my friend gets done with him, he's going to be even more disturbed", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Sure it is", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "This 1966 maroon that place 500. You driving this car", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Bullshit. It's mine, motherfucker", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Where's that", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "my friend? Where's my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I never heard of it", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Your father worked in a mannequin factory", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "The hell I am", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I never said that", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " Professor my friend", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "my friend. This is my wife my friend", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Otherwise we would've been here earlier", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Well, certainly we'll reimburse you", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "my friend said it sounded like something my friend would be messed up in", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Who does", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Ah. Wait a minute. The university must know where he lives", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Is it a little late to call the Chancellor", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " Who's this ", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Don't worry, my friend, I'll figure something out", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I'm a little worried, my friend", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": " You didn't happen to call the house last night, did you, my friend", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "And what do you think you might have said", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "I think I might have", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "I think I might've said I was in love with you", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "He told me", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I said it didn't sound like you", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "'That's my car, motherfucker.", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "...we find the jacket", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Who's got a gun", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": " Move away, cupcake.  He's got a gun", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "You've got a gun, motherfucker. Drop it", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Shut up.  Cupcake. Please. Inside", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "I'm going to shoot him. If he doesn't put that gun down", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "my friend isn't going to send my friend to jail, Crabs. I know that", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "No. But I don't think that matters", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "I passed out", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "I've been doing that a lot lately", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "You did", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "So I hear. You've also been smoking a lot of marijuana, I understand", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "So I hear. You've also been smoking a lot of marijuana, I understand", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "How long have you been having them", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "She told you about. . ", "docId": "thewonderboys.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "Actually, it was her husband's dog..", "qsentId": 62}]